

CONTACT DETAILS

179B West Street, Fareham Hampshire, PO16 0EF

conorcresswell94@gmail.com 07808274195 conorcresswell.github.ic

EDUCATION

University of Winchester (2013 – 2017)

MA (Hons) in Digital Media Practice. Graduated with Merit. BA (Hons) in Digital Media Design. Graduated with First Class Honours.

Chalfonts Community College (2006 – 2013)

3 A-Levels: Photography (C), Applied ICT (C) and Design & Technology: Product Design 3D (E)
10 GCSEs grades A-C including
English (B) and Maths (B)
1 Diploma grade B in Level 2 Creative and Media

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.

../in/conorcresswell



ConorCresswell

Bē

conorcresswell



ABOUT

A self-motivated and productive designer currently working as a Digital Designer for Stepstone UK looking to further my learning within a similar position. With over two years' experience as a design practitioner creating an array of high-quality digital products using the Adobe Creative Cloud and HTML/CSS/JavaScript. Recognised by his peers as a highly skilled designer with his email designs, with an enthusiasm for learning and a strong work ethic.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)
- Responsive Website Design
- Email Design using HTML/CSS
- Understanding of Brand Identity and User Experience
- Microsoft Office
- PC and Mac Fluent

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Strong Project Manager
- Confident Problem Solver
- Effective Brand Communicator
- Proactive Learner
- Excellent Multi-Tasker

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Digital Designer - Stepstone UK, Havant (August 2017 to Present)

Duties:

- Resizing and retouching external clients' marketing material using Adobe Photoshop.
- Responsive email design and production using HTML, CSS, and JavaScipt.
- Basic front-end development of small, one-page websites using a responsive HTML/CSS framework.
- Designed informative, interactive, and multi-page training guides for office processes on the Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign).
- Implementing project management software like Trello and Microsoft Planner into the team's workflow.

Freelance Graphic Designer/Illustrator - Sprechen Digital Marketing, Winchester (March 2015 to April 2017)

Duties:

- Rebuilding existing clients' logos as vector images using Adobe Illustrator.
- Ensuring that all new designs adhere to company values and guidelines.
- Improving clients' brands by designing logos, banners, and vector illustrations ready for web use.
- Communicating directly with stakeholders to build briefs and plans of action.

Design and Animation Intern - Bravo Post Production, London (July 2015 to August 2015)

Duties

- Using Adobe Photoshop to create animation storyboards collaboratively with other team members.
- Expanded my owns skills in Adobe After Effects to create simple motion graphics.